https://www.unt.edu/privacy

Google search
HomeAdmissionsAcademicsStudent LifeAbout UNTResearchLocationsAthleticsGiving
Privacy
CORONAVIRUS (COVID-19) UPDATES
Click here to learn more
In an effort to keep everyone healthy, we now are offering our services remotely. Please stay connected.
Get the Latest Updates | Help UNT Students | Read Stories of Resilience and Caring
Privacy Statement
This Web site (http://www.unt.edu/) uses browser detection to determine the browser type and browser version of site visitors. This information is used only in its aggregate form, to help us further refine our web site design. The remote host name is collected from each site visitor, and is used only to provide statistical data, specifically, the percentage of "hits" from the UNT domain vs. the percentage of "hits" from outside the UNT domain for this Web site. The pages accessed by each visitor are recorded and preserved in an aggregate form to provide us with information about the relative usage of the pages in our Web site. The web page that referred the site visitor to this UNT Web site is also recorded, and used to improve overall site navigation.
Email messages sent to the email contact for this Web site will be answered by that account holder or forwarded to another individual at UNT to be answered. Email messages sent to the email contact for this Web site and copies of replies sent by this email contact may be kept and reviewed to help ensure the relevance of information presented in this Web site and the usefulness of the replies from the email contact.
Privacy Statement Requirements
Privacy Policy
(Excerpted from the web Publishing Policy)
All UNT web sites must provide a privacy statement on their top-level web
page (also called home or index pages). Each privacy statement must identify the information collected from site visitors, describe its use, and assure site visitors of the integrity of their information during transmission and storage.
Privacy Notice
Each privacy statement must identify both passive and active information
collected from site visitors and describe its use. Passive information is collected without alerting the site visitor. Active information is purposely provided by the site visitor.
Examples of passive information include:
browser detection: browser type and browser version
remote host name: the DNS entry for the computer accessing the web site
cookies: hidden identifiers used to store data during a visit, and cumulatively over time
Examples of active information include:
name of the site visitor
e-mail address of the site visitor
comments or answers to questions provided by the site visitor
Security of Private Information
Each
web site at UNT will assure site visitors of the integrity of their
information, in transit and in storage. This assurance should include
whether or not the data is encrypted in transit via Secure Socket Layers (SSL) or Transport Layer Security (TLS), the positions or UNT
employees that will be able to access the information, and under what
conditions that information will be accessed.
Because
the university has special responsibilities to protect students'
information under the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act, any
university web site collecting data falling under FERPA guidelines must
carefully review its handling of such data and insure that its
procedures adhere to the act.
Examples of Privacy Statements
Example 1:
This web site (https://online.unt.edu/)
uses browser detection to determine the browser type and browser version of site visitors. This information is used only in its
aggregate form, to help us further refine our web site design. The
remote host name is collected from each site visitor, and is used only
to provide statistical data, specifically, the percentage of "hits"
from the UNT domain vs. the percentage of "hits" from outside the UNT
domain for this web site. The pages accessed by each visitor are
recorded and preserved in an aggregate form to provide us with
information about the relative usage of the pages in our web site. The
web page that referred the site visitor to this UNT web site is also
recorded, and used to improve overall site navigation.
E-mail
messages sent to the e-mail contact for this web site will be answered
by that account holder or forwarded to another individual at UNT to be
answered. e-mail messages sent to the e-mail contact for this web site
and copies of replies sent by this e-mail contact may be kept and
reviewed to help ensure the relevance of information presented in this
web site and the usefulness of the replies from the e-mail contact.
Example 2:
This web site (https://online.unt.edu/)
uses browser detection to determine the browser type and browser
version of site visitors. This information is used only in its
aggregate form, to help us further refine our web site design. The
remote host name is collected from each site visitor, and is used only
to provide statistical data, specifically, the percentage of "hits"
from the UNT domain vs. the percentage of "hits" from outside the UNT
domain for this web site. The pages accessed by each visitor are
recorded and preserved in an aggregate form to provide us with
information about the relative usage of the pages in our web site. The
web page that referred the site visitor to this UNT web site is also
recorded, and used to improve overall site navigation.
E-mail
messages sent to the e-mail contact for this web site will be answered
by that account holder or forwarded to another individual at UNT to be
answered. e-mail messages sent to the e-mail contact for this web site
and copies of replies sent by this e-mail contact may be kept and
reviewed to help ensure the relevance of information presented in this
web site and the usefulness of the replies from the e-mail contact.
Students
and instructors that log in to Blackboard Vista classes have more detailed
records. Once logged in with a Blackboard Vista User ID, the browser, browser
version, remote host and Blackboard Vista User ID will be tracked throughout Blackboard Vista
class activities. All actions taken by that Blackboard Vista User ID in a Blackboard Vista
class are logged and accessible by the Blackboard Vista Course instructor and the
Blackboard Vista System Administrator (at the request of the Blackboard Vista Course
instructor or in the course of diagnosing a technical difficulty).
Blackboard Vista courses are archived once a semester on the day after grades are
due. These archives are kept on tape backup for at least five years. Blackboard Vista course archives are accessible by the Blackboard Vista System Administrator,
and will be accessed only in the event of a request from the instructor
of that course or governing body of the university, or in the course of
diagnosing a technical difficulty.
Top
